https://www.wolverinedata.com/privacy-policy

Cart: 0 items
Go!
Home
Products
Digital Image Converters & Scanners
Audio and More!
Wolverinedata's Privacy Policy
Wolverinedata respects your privacy. Across our business, around the world, we will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes. We use your information to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example, to process your purchase, provide service and support, and share product, service and company news and offerings with you. We do not sell your personal information. We only share your personal data outside the Wolverinedata family of companies with your consent, as required by law or to protect Wolverinedata, its customers, or the public, or with companies that help Wolverinedata fulfill its obligations with you, and then only with partners who share Wolverinedata's commitment to protecting your privacy and data. At any time you may contact Wolverinedata with any privacy questions or concerns you may have. You also may ask at any time to see the data you have given us and request correction or deletion. Our goal is to ensure the highest levels of security and confidentiality.
Privacy and Data Security
At Wolverinedata, your right to privacy and data security is a primary concern. That's why, when you visit Wolverinedata.com, we help you maintain control over your personal data on the Internet. Below are the guidelines we use for protecting the information you provide us during a visit to our Internet site or when you use our online support offerings or support applications loaded on your computer. Wolverinedata follows the regulations set by BBB OnLine® Privacy Program. The BBB OnLine Privacy Program is backed by an organization noted for its expertise and experience in conducting successful national self-regulation programs--the Council of Better Business Bureaus. The mission of BBB OnLine is to promote trust and confidence on the Internet by advocating ethical online business practices. Further information about this program is available at http://www.bbbonLine.org.
Wolverinedata's Privacy statement discloses the privacy guidelines for the entire domestic Wolverinedata Web site. The guidelines at this site are applicable only to this domestic Web site. Information submitted solely in a business capacity is not covered by these guidelines.
Wolverinedata only asks for specific types of personal information
In a few areas on our Web site and online customer support tools, we ask you to provide information that will enable us to enhance your site visit, to assist you with technical support issues or to follow up with you after your visit. It is completely optional for you to participate.
For example, we request information from you when you:
Place an order
Provide feedback in an online survey
Participate in a sweepstakes or other promotional offer
Request e-mail notification of your order status.
Subscribe to a newsletter or a mailing list
Fill out a support request
In each of the instances above, we may ask for your name, e-mail address, phone number, address, type of business, customer preference information, customer number and service tag number, as well as other similar personal information that is needed to register or subscribe you to services or offers. If we ever ask for significantly different information we will inform you. In the case of newsletters or mailing lists, you will be able to "unsubscribe" to these mailings at any time.
Wolverinedata only uses your personal information for specific purposes
The information you provide will be kept confidential and used to support your customer relationship with Wolverinedata. Among other things, we want to help you quickly find information on Wolverinedata.com and alert you to product upgrades, special offers, updated information and other new products and services from Wolverinedata. Agents or contractors of Wolverinedata who have access to your personal information and prospect information are required to keep the information confidential and not use it for any other purpose than to carry out the services they are performing for Wolverinedata. Wolverinedata may enhance or merge your information collected at its site with data from third parties for purposes of marketing products or services to you.
In addition, Wolverinedata may be required to disclose personal information in connection with law enforcement, fraud prevention, regulation, and other legal action or if Wolverinedata reasonably believes it is necessary to do so to protect Wolverinedata, its customers, or the public.
You can opt-out of receiving further marketing from Wolverinedata at any time
Periodically, we may send you information about our various products and services, or other products and services we feel may be of interest to you. Only Wolverinedata (or agents working on behalf of Wolverinedata and under confidentiality agreements) will send you these direct mailings. If you do not want to receive such mailings, simply tell us when you give us your personal information. Or, at any time you can easily opt-out of receiving further marketing from Wolverinedata by emailing us with an unsubscribe note at support@wolverinedata.com.
Wolverinedata will not disclose your personal information to any outside organization for its use in marketing without your consent
Information regarding you (such as name, address and phone number) or your order and the products you purchase will not be given or sold to any outside organization for its use in marketing or solicitation without your consent. Your information may be shared with agents or contractors of Wolverinedata for the purpose of performing services for Wolverinedata.
Internet Commerce
The online store at Wolverinedata.com is designed to give you options concerning the privacy of your credit card information, name, address, e-mail and any other information you provide us. Wolverinedata is committed to data security with respect to information collected on our site. We offer the industry standard security measures available through your browser called SSL encryption, (please see Wolverinedata's Security page for details on these security measures). If at any time you would like to make a purchase, but do not want to provide your credit card information online, you may contact a sales representative over the telephone. It has always been a Wolverinedata practice to contact customers in the event of a potential problem with your purchase or any normal business communication regarding your purchase.
Customized Experience
New technologies are emerging on the Internet that help us deliver customized visitor experiences. At Wolverinedata, we may use "cookies" to help us determine which service and support information is appropriate to your machine and to maintain your shopping experience in our online store. Our use of this technology does not mean that we automatically know any information about you. We might be able to ascertain what type of computer you are using, but beyond that, our use of cookies is designed only to provide you with a better experience when using http://www.Wolverinedata.com. Wolverinedata has no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using the Wolverinedata.com site.
